Guide to the UE National Office Records Relating to District 2 and District 2 Locals, 1936-1994 UE.4.1.2
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- District 2 Locals, 2.
  - Local 213
    - Local 213 Incoming Correspondence, September 21, 1939-April 26, 1943 (Box 8, Folder 48)
      - Emspak to Roy Peterson Regarding Films, March 13, 1941; 8.
      - Emspak to Gilbert Moline Regarding Factionalism and United Front, April 4, 1941; 9.
      - Emspak to Ferriter Regarding Contracts, April 19, 1941; 10.
      - Emspak Telegram to Moline, May 7, 1941; 11.
      - Emspak to Ferriter Regarding Stone and Allied Products Workers, May 8, 1941; 12.
      - Emspak to Tortoriello Regarding Finances, May 9, 1941; 13.
      - Emspak to Frederick Pyne Regarding UE News, June 16, 1941; 14.
      - Emspak to Ferriter Regarding United Auto Workers, September 30, 1941; 15.
      - Emspak to Ferriter Regarding Local 213 Constitution, November 7, 1941; 16.
      - Emspak to John Jekot, December 5, 1941; 17.
      - Emspak to Jekot Regarding Mailing List, December 10, 1941; 18.
      - Emspak to Jekot Regarding Local 213 Constitution, April 6, 1942; 19.
      - Emspak to Jekot, June 8, 1942; 20.
      - Emspak Telegram to Ferriter, June 18, 1942; 21.
    - Local 213 Incoming Correspondence, April 2, 1941-July 21, 1944 (Box 8, Folder 49)
      - Albert Fitzgerald to Thomas Ferriter Regarding Local 213 Officers, December 23, 1941; 1.
      - Fitzgerald Telegram to Ferriter, June 19, 1942; 2.
      - Fitzgerald to Helen Bushow Regarding Local 213 Officers, January 5, 1943; 3.
      - Fitzgerald's Secretary to John Jekot Regarding Local 213 Sixth Anniversary Celebration, June 9, 1943; 4.
      - Fitzgerald Telegram to Lawrence Locke Regarding Ferriter Farewell Dinner, August 12, 1943; 5.
      - Nat Geller to Tom Cahill Regarding Dues Check-off, October 6, 1942; 6.
      - James Matles to Gilbert Moline, April 2, 1941; 7.
      - Matles to Jekot Regarding Local 213 Van Norman Machine Tool Contracts, September 4, 1941; 8.
      - Matles Telegram to Ferriter, January 14, 1942; 9.
      - Matles to Ferriter Regarding Overtime, October 8, 1942; 10.
      - Matles to Locke Regarding Overtime, April 15, 1942; 11.
      - Matles to Locke Regarding Overtime and Dictograph Sales, July 7, 1943; 12.
      - Nat Spero to Harry McIntire Regarding Holidays and War Labor Board, July 21, 1944; 13.
    - Local 213 Outgoing Correspondence, August 21, 1939-November 5, 1949 (Box 8, Folder 50)
      - Helen Burshaw to Albert Fitzgerald Regarding Local 213 Officers, December 21, 1945; 1.
      - Emil Carlson to Julius Emspak Regarding Supplies, August 21, 1939; 2.
      - Thomas Ferriter to Emspak Regarding Women and Ladies Auxiliary, March 1, 1941; 3.
      - Ferriter to James Matles Regarding Membership Meeting, May 5, 1941; 4.
      - Ferriter to Emspak Regarding Quarry Workers Union, May 7, 1941; 5.
      - Ferriter to Emspak Regarding Local 214 Van Norman Contracts, July 17, 1941; 6.
      - Ferriter Telegram to Matles Regarding Local 213 Van Norman Collective Bargaining, August 9, 1941; 7.
      - Ferriter to Emspak Regarding United Auto Workers, August 21, 1941; 8.
      - Ferriter to Fitzgerald Regarding Local 213 Constitution and Dues, October 27, 1941; 9.
      - Ferriter to Emspak Regarding Supplies, November 4, 1941; 10.
      - Ferriter to Fitzgerald Regarding Local 213 Officers, December 9, 1941; 11.
      - Ferriter to Emspak Regarding Local 213 Officers, December 9, 1941; 12.
      - Ferriter Telegram to Fitzgerald Regarding No Strike Pledge and War Labor Board, March 14, 1943; 13.
      - John Jekot to Emspak Regarding Political Action, August 21, 1941; 14.
      - Jekot to Emspak Regarding Local 213 Van Norman Contracts, August 28, 1941; 15.
      - Jekot to Emspak Regarding Local 213 Officers, December 2, 1941; 16.
      - Jekot to Emspak Regarding Local 213 Van Norman Collective Bargaining and Union Shop, April 17, 1942; 17.
      - Jekot to Emspak Regarding Factionalism and Local 213 Officer Elections, June 3, 1942; 18.
      - Jekot to Matles Regarding Wages, December 29, 1942; 19.
      - Jekot Telegram to Fitzgerald Regarding Local 213 Anniversary Celebration, June 9, 1942; 20.
      - Jekot to UE Regarding Political Action Committee, November 5, 1949; 21.
      - Jekot to Fitzgerald Regarding Local 213 Van Norman Strike, May 25, 1948; 22.
      - Jekot to Leo Hunderup Regarding Local 213 Van Norman Strike, May 26, 1948; 23.
    - Local 213 Outgoing Correspondence, February 27, 1941-December 11, 1944 (Box 8, Folder 51)
      - Lawrence Locke to James Matles Regarding War Labor Board and Local 213 Van Norman Collective Bargaining, March 18, 1943; 1.
      - Locke to Matles Regarding Political Action, Little Steel Formula and Inflation with Press Release, April 11, 1943; 2.
      - Locke to Matles Regarding Executive Order 9246, Overtime and Political Action, June 17, 1943; 3.
      - Locke to Matles Regarding 1943 UE Convention, June 21, 1943; 4.
      - Locke Telegram to Albert Fitzgerald Regarding Conscription and Ferrister Testimonial, August 1943; 5.
      - Locke Telegram to Matles Regarding Conscription and Ferriter Testimonial, August 1943; 6.
      - Locke Telegram to Julius Emspak Regarding Conscription and Ferriter Testimonial, August 1943; 7.
      - Locke to Fitzgerald Regarding Conscription and Ferriter Testimonial, August 10, 1943; 8.
      - Locke to Emspak Regarding Unemployment and Reconversion, September 2, 1943; 9.
      - Harry McIntire to Emspak Regarding Holiday, July 20, 1944; 10.
      - McIntire to Emspak Regarding Staff Finances, December 11, 1944; 11.
      - Gilbert Moline to Matles Regarding Local 213 Van Norman Collective Bargaining, March 27, 1941; 12.
      - Moline to Matles, April 9, 1941; 13.
      - Moline to Emspak Regarding 1941 UE Convention, July 9, 1941; 14.
      - Moline Telegram to Emspak, 15.
      - Roy Peterson to Emspak Regarding Films, March 11, 1941; 16.
      - Estelle Stadnicki to Emspak Regarding Local 213 Officers, October 16-November 9, 1943; 17-18.
      - Stadnicki to Emspak Regarding 1944 UE Convention, July 26, 1944; 19.
      - John Tortoriello to Emspak Regarding Finances, February 27, 1941; 20.
      - Tortoriello to Emspak Regarding Mailing List, May 23, 1941; 21.
    - Local 213 Salary and Expense Letters, December 26, 1940-January 9, 1946 (Box 8, Folder 52)
      - Emil Carlson, December 26, 1940; 1.
      - Jack Tortoriello, February 19-December 1, 1941; 2-13.
      - Roy Peterson, January 9, 1946; 14.
    - Local 213 Collective Bargaining, May 15-17, 1941 (Box 8, Folder 53)
      - Thomas Ferriter to Emspak with Proposed Contract and Company Offer, May 15, 1941; 1.
      - Emspak to Ferriter, May 17, 1941; 2.
    - Local 213 Collective Bargaining, July 14-16, 1941 (Box 8, Folder 54)
      - Thomas Ferriter to Julius Emspak with 1942 Proposed Agreement, July 14, 1941; 1.
      - Emspak to Ferriter, July 16, 1941; 2.
    - Local 213 Productivity, September 23-October 21, 1943 (Box 8, Folder 55)
      - Lawrence Locke to Julius Emspak with "Memo on the Full Utilization of the Production Facilities of Van Norman Machine Tool" and "List of Machines at Van Norman Machine Tool", September 23, 1943; 1.
      - Emspak Letter to Locke, October 21, 1943; 2.
    - Local 213 Per Capita, July 24-August 7, 1944 (Box 8, Folder 56)
      - Richard Linsley to Julius Emspak, July 24, 1944; 1.
      - Emspak's Secretary to Linsley, August 7, 1944; 2.
    - Local 213 Van Norman, October 13, 1949-November 16, 1950 (Box 8, Folder 57)
    - Local 214 Correspondence, September 24, 1941-January 14, 1942 (Box 8, Folder 58)
      - George Addes to Julius Emspak Regarding Springfield, September 24, 1941; 1.
      - Telephone Call Memo to Thomas Ferriter Regarding Prices, January 14, 1942; 2.
      - James Matles Telegram to John Steelman Regarding Local 213 Van Norman Tool Collective Bargaining, January 14, 1942; 3.
  - Local 214
    - Local 214 Officers Lists, September 12, 1943-April 6, 1954 (Box 8, Folder 59)
    - Local 214 Incoming Correspondence, October 8, 1943-February 17, 1954 (Box 8, Folder 60)
      - Julius Emspak to Flora Foley Regarding Finances, October 8, 1943; 1.
      - Emspak to Lewis Lehman Regarding Holtzer-Cabot, October 15, 1943; 2.
      - Emspak to Foley Regarding Organization, June 1, 1945; 3.
      - Emspak to Charles Beckwith Regarding Finances, December 10, 1946; 4.
      - Emspak to Leo Driscoll Regarding Finances, December 16, 1946; 5.
      - Emspak to Beckwith Regarding Per Capita Payments, January 8, 1947; 6.
      - Emspak to Beckwith Regarding Finances, January 9, 1947; 7.
      - Emspak to Irene Deleor Regarding Finances, October 30, 1950; 8.
      - Emspak to Francis Kepple Regarding Finances, February 17, 1954; 9.
    - Local 214 Outgoing Correspondence, September 21, 1943-July 5, 1949 (Box 8, Folder 61)
      - Charles Beckwith to Julius Emspak Regarding Finances, December 13, 1944; 1.
      - Beckwith to Emspak Regarding Finances, 2.
      - J. Leo Driscoll to Emspak Regarding Finances, December 4, 1946; 3.
      - Driscoll to Emspak Regarding Finances with July 13, 1949, Emspak Letter to Driscoll, July 5, 1949; 4.
      - Flora Foley to Emspak Regarding Supplies and Finances, September 21, 1943; 5.
      - Foley to Emspak Regarding Supplies, January 5, 1944; 6.
      - Foley to Emspak Regarding National Labor Relations Board, Unfair Labor Practices and Dismissals, 7.
      - Lewis Lehman to Emspak Regarding Staff Members, October 5, 1943; 8.
      - Eleanor Snyder to Emspak Regarding Unemployment, April 1946; 9.
    - Local 214 Financial Secretary Reports, October 1943-October 1945 (Box 8, Folder 62)
    - Local 214 Financial Secretary Reports, October 1946-July 1951 (Box 8, Folder 63)
    - Local 214 Organization, September 2-20, 1943 (Box 8, Folder 64)
      - Allan McNeil to Julius Emspak, September 2, 1943; 1.
      - Emspak Telegram to McNeil, September 7, 1943; 2.
      - McNeil Telegram to Emspak, September 7, 1943; 3.
      - Emspak to McNeil, September 20, 1943; 4.
      - Emspak to John Murphy, September 20, 1943; 5.
      - Emspak to McNeil, September 20, 1943; 6.
    - Local 214 McGillicuddy Firing, May 7-15, 1945 (Box 8, Folder 65)
      - Julius Emspak to Richard Linsley with Flora Foley Letter to Emspak, May 7, 1945; 1.
      - Linsley to Ray Klausner, May 15, 1945; 2.
    - Local 214 Membership Meeting, January 19-27, 1954 (Box 8, Folder 66)
      - Paul Seymour to Albert Fitzgerald, January 19, 1954; 1.
      - Fitzgerald to Seymour, January 27, 1954; 2.
    - Local 214 IUE Inter-union Rivalry, December 2-6, 1954 (Box 8, Folder 67)
      - Donald Tormey to James Matles, December 2, 1954; 1.
      - Matles to Tormey, December 6, 1954; 2.
    - Local 214 Correspondence, May 22, 1946-February 9, 1955 (Box 8, Folder 68)
      - Donald Tormey to Julius Emspak Regarding Unemployment, May 22, 1946; 1.
      - Paul Seymour to James Matles Regarding IUE Inter-union Rivalry and Check-off, February 9, 1955; 2.
  - Local 215
    - Local 215 Officers Lists, April 12, 1937-January 15, 1949 (Box 8, Folder 69)
    - Local 215 Incoming Correspondence, November 12, 1940-May 28, 1946 (Box 8, Folder 70)
      - Julius Emspak to Godfrey Prout Regarding Mailing List, November 12, 1940-December 11, 1941; 1-5.
      - Emspak to George MacRae Regarding Supplies, January 19, 1943; 6.
      - Emspak to Margaret Young Regarding Consolidated Lamp, May 20, 1943; 7.
      - Emspak to Prout Regarding Finances, March 7, 1945; 8.
      - Emspak to Muriel Archer Regarding Finances, March 19, 1946; 9.
      - Emspak to Doris Reichardt Regarding Finances and Veterans, May 28, 1946; 10.
    - Local 215 Outgoing Correspondence, November 21, 1941-March 9, 1946 (Box 8, Folder 71)
      - Muriel Archer to Julius Emspak Regarding Local 215 Officers, March 9, 1946; 1.
      - George MacRae to James Matles Regarding Overtime, January 15, 1943; 2.
      - MacRae to Emspak Regarding Local 215 Officers, January 15, 1943; 3.
      - Godfrey Prout to Emspak Regarding Finances, November 21, 1941; 4.
      - Roger Thompson to Emspak Regarding Local 215 Officers, October 5, 1942; 5.
      - Margaret Young to Emspak Regarding Local 215 Officers, April 22, 1943; 6.
    - Local 215 Salary and Expense Letters, Godfrey Prout, April 2-October 6, 1941 (Box 8, Folder 72)
    - Local 215 Volcan Electric Financial Report, December 1943 (Box 8, Folder 73)
      - David Bennett to Julius Emspak, December 1943; 1.
      - A.N. Towsen to Bennett, December 14, 1943; 2.
    - Local 215 Federated Council of Lynn, December 1, 1943-May 15, 1944 (Box 8, Folder 74)
      - Margaret Young to Julius Emspak, December 1, 1943; 1.
      - David Bennett to Emspak, December 1943; 2.
      - Emspak to Richard Linsley, December 13, 1943; 3.
      - Emspak to Bennett, December 13, 1943; 4.
      - Young to Emspak, December 14, 1943; 5.
      - Bennett to Emspak, December 1943; 6.
      - Emspak to Linsley, December 17, 1943; 7.
      - Emspak to Young, December 21, 1943; 8.
      - Emspak to Harry Kinney, December 21, 1943-January 6, 1944; 9-10.
      - Kinney to Emspak, March 8, 1944; 11.
      - Young to Emspak, March 13, 1944; 12.
      - Bennett to Emspak, March 15, 1944; 13.
    - Local 215 Political Action Committee, September 24-October 16, 1946 (Box 8, Folder 75)
      - Paul Seymour to Julius Emspak, September 24, 1946; 1.
      - Elinore Parnes to Emspak, October 1, 1946; 2.
      - Munel Bollen to George Rettinger, October 16, 1946; 3.
  - Local 216
    - Local 216 Incoming Correspondence, August 17, 1939-May 19, 1953 (Box 8, Folder 76)
      - Julius Emspak to Ralph Kinney Regarding Supplies with Ledger and Statement on Unemployment, Dues and Initiation Stamps, August 17, 1939; 1.
      - Emspak to Jack Schubert Regarding Organization, February 28, 1941; 2.
      - Emspak to George WIlson Regarding Thompson Gibbs, March 18, 1941; 3.
      - Emspak to John Grant Regarding Mailing List, May 16, 1941; 4.
      - Emspak to Albert Metzger Regarding Local 216 Thompson Gibb Contracts and Local 216 Constitution, October 31, 1941; 5.
      - Emspak to Thomas Gooley Regarding Finances, March 26, 1945; 6.
      - Emspak to Charles Keller Regarding Veterans and Finances, August 9, 1945; 7.
      - Emspak to Vincent Kent Regarding Per Capita Payments, January 21, 1947; 8.
      - Emspak to George Grant Regarding Finances, October 17, 1951; 9.
      - Emspak to William Brown Regarding UE Fighting Fund, November 10, 1952; 10.
      - Emspak to Brown Regarding Finances, May 19, 1953; 11.
    - Local 216 Outgoing Correspondence, March 13, 1941-May 12, 1953 (Box 8, Folder 77)
      - William Brown to UE Regarding Finances, May 12, 1953; 1.
      - George Grant to UE Regarding Finances, April 22, 1948; 2.
      - Grant to Julius Emspak Regarding Finances, October 6, 1951; 3.
      - Charles Keller to Emspak Regarding Veterans and Finances, August 3, 1945; 4.
      - Harry Kinney to Emspak Regarding Finances and Lynn Federated Council, December 8, 1943; 5.
      - Kinney to Emspak Regarding Local 216 Officers and Finances, January 15, 1944; 6.
      - Gill McLoughlin to Emspak Regarding Unemployment and Wages, July 26, 1948; 7.
      - Albert Metzgen to Emspak Regarding Local 216 Thompson Gibb Contracts, October 19, 1941; 8.
      - George Wilson to Emspak Regarding Finances and Thompson Gibb, March 13, 1941; 9.
    - Local 216 Salem Correspondence, January 28, 1957-January 17, 1972 (Box 8, Folder 78)
    - Local 216 Salary and Expense Letters, John Grant, May 5-23, 1941 (Box 8, Folder 79)
    - Local 216 Lynn 710 Forms, February 5, 1948-May 19, 1971 (Box 8, Folder 80)
  - Local 217
    - Local 217 Officers Lists, March 24, 1944-October 1, 1949 (Box 8, Folder 81)
    - Local 217 Incoming Correspondence, October 20, 1943-October 26, 1944 (Box 8, Folder 82)
      - Julius Emspak to Meuse Regarding Finances, October 20, 1943; 1.
      - Emspak to William Marchall Regarding Finances, October 26, 1944; 2.
    - Local 217 Outgoing Correspondnece, February 1-October 29, 1944 (Box 8, Folder 83)
      - William Marchall to Julius Emspak Regarding Supplies, Finances and Conscription, February 1, 1944; 1.
      - Marchall to Emspak Regarding Finances, October 29, 1944; 2.
    - Local 217 Organization, October 18-20, 1943 (Box 8, Folder 84)
      - Richard Linsley to Julius Emspak, October 18, 1943; 1.
      - Emspak to Linsley, October 20, 1943; 2.
      - Emspak to John Murphy, October 20, 1943; 3.
    - Local 217 Financial Arrangements, October 11-November 2, 1944 (Box 8, Folder 85)
      - Donald Tormey to Julius Emspak, October 11-20, 1944; 1-2.
      - Ray Klausner to Tormey, October 23, 1944; 3.
      - Emspak to Albert Olsen, November 2, 1944; 4.
    - Local 217 Elliot Rosenberg Address, February 5-8, 1951 (Box 8, Folder 86)
  - Local 218
    - Local 218 Officers, Lists, November 14, 1944 (Box 8, Folder 87)
    - Local 218 Incoming Correspondence, January 3, 1944-December 12, 1945 (Box 8, Folder 88)
      - Janet Barish to Harold Hastings Regarding Finances, November 16, 1945; 1.
      - Barish to Albert Burton Regarding Finances, December 12, 1945; 2.
      - Julius Emspak to Clair Cook Regarding Finances, January 3, 1944; 3.
      - Emspak to Fred Snow Regarding Finances, February 11, 1944; 4.
      - Emspak to Snow Regarding Local 218 News, Finances and Staff Members, September 12, 1944; 5.
      - Emspak to Snow Regarding Fellows Gear Shaper, September 1, 1944; 6.
      - Emspak Telegram to Snow Regarding 1944 UE Convention, September 19, 1944; 7.
      - Emspak to K.A. Bladyka Regarding Finances, October 5, 1944; 8.
      - Emspak to Snow Regarding Finances, October 13, 1944; 9.
      - Emspak to Snow Regarding Local 218 Officers and Finances, October 24, 1944; 10.
      - Emspak to Snow Regarding Local 218 News and Fellows Gear Shaper, October 25, 1944; 11.
      - Ruth Shubert to George Tully Regarding West Coast Migration, November 24, 1944; 12.
      - Emspak to Cook Regarding Finances, November 30, 1944; 13.
      - Emspak's Secretary to Cook Regarding Finances, December 15, 1944; 14.
      - Emspak to Cook Regarding Finances, December 21, 1944-February 7, 1945; 15-18.
      - Emspak to Cook Regarding Veterans and Finances, February 13, 1945; 19.
      - Emspak to Cook Regarding Finances, February 20, 1945; 20.
      - Shubert to Cook Regarding Publicity, March 3, 1945; 21.
      - Emspak to Cook, April 2, 1945; 22.
      - Emspak to Tully Regarding Finances, May 8, 1945; 23.
      - Emspak to Hastings Regarding Finances, July 9, 1945; 24.
      - Emspak to Tully Regarding Finances, July 25, 1945; 25.
    - Local 218 Incoming Correspondence, August 18, 1944-March 3, 1955 (Box 8, Folder 89)
      - Julius Emspak to George Tully, July 31, 1945; 1.
      - Emspak to Albert Burton Regarding Finances and Organization, May 24, 1946; 2.
      - Emspak to Harold Hastings Regarding Mailing List, December 27, 1946; 3.
      - Emspak to Henry Hicks Regarding Finances, July 30, 1947; 4.
      - Emspak to Ralph Howard Regarding Political Action Committee, October 8, 1947; 5.
      - Emspak to Hastings Regarding Political Action Committee, October 15, 1947; 6.
      - Emspak to Hastings Regarding Finances, November 27, 1950; 7.
      - Emspak to Robert Green Regarding UE Fighting Fund, November 5-18, 1952; 8-9.
      - Albert Fitzgerald to Mrs. Walter Curtis Regarding Membership Transfer, January 16, 1948; 10.
      - James Matles to Burton Regarding Finances and Organization, June 4, 1946; 11.
      - Matles to Burton Regarding Finances, July 16, 1946; 12.
      - Matles to Hicks Regarding Finances and Factionalism, October 10, 1947; 13.
      - Matles to Harold Hayes Regarding Finances, November 3, 1947; 14.
      - Matles to Hicks Regarding Local 218 Collective Bargaining and Membership Meeting, March 3, 1955; 15.
      - Russ Nixon to Hicks Regarding Political Action Committee, October 8-November 17, 1947; 16-18.
      - Don Pinkston Telegram to Hicks Regarding Publicity, April 10, 1947; 19.
      - Jack Simon to Constantine Bladyka Regarding National Labor Relations Board, August 18, 1944; 20.
    - Local 218 Outgoing Correspondence, September 22, 1944-April 22, 1948 (Box 8, Folder 90)
      - K.A. Bladyka to Julius Emspak Regarding Finances, September 22, 1944; 1.
      - Barbara Brown to Emspak Regarding Finances, April 22, 1948; 2.
      - Albert Burton to Emspak Regarding Finances and Mailing List, August 1945; 3.
      - Burton to Janet Barish Regarding Finances, November 27, 1945; 4.
      - Burton to Emspak Regarding Finances and Unemployment, May 10, 1946; 5.
      - Burton to Emspak Regarding Morre and Thompson Organization, May 1946; 6.
      - Burton to James Matles Regarding Organization and Finances, May 29, 1946; 7.
      - Burton to UE Regarding Organization and Unemployment, August 1946; 8.
      - Burton to Emspak Regarding Organization with July Expenses, September 10, 1946; 9.
      - Burton to UE Regarding Organization and Jones and Lamson National Labor Relations Board Elections, October 1946; 10.
      - Burton to Emspak Regarding Political Action Committee, October 18, 1946; 11.
      - Clair Cook to Emspak Regarding Finances with Bills, October 27, 1944; 12.
      - Cook to Emspak Regarding Supplies and Finances, November 14, 1944; 13.
      - Cook to Emspak Regarding Finances, November 20, 1944; 14.
    - Local 218 Outgoing Correspondence, December 1, 1944-October 2, 1952 (Box 8, Folder 91)
      - Clair Cook to Julius Emspak Regarding Finances, December 1, 1944; 1.
      - Cook to UE Regarding Staff Finances, December 7, 1944; 2.
      - Cook to Emspak Regarding Finances, December 22, 1944; 3.
      - Cook to Emspak Regarding Veterans and Finances, January 10-February 9, 1945; 4-5.
      - Cook to UE Regarding Publicity, February 26, 1945; 6.
      - Mrs. Walter Curtis to UE Regarding Injuries and Transfers, January 13, 1948; 7.
      - Harold Hastings to Emspak Regarding Finances, Dues and Local 218 Jones and Lawson and Vermont Foundries Collective Bargaining, July 3, 1945; 8.
      - Hastings to Emspak Regarding Twin State Labor News, December 5, 1946; 9.
      - Hastings to Emspak Regarding Finances, November 2, 1949; 10.
      - Henry Hicks to Emspak Regarding Supplies, April 2, 1947; 11.
      - Hicks to Emspak Regarding Finances with June 12, 1947, Supply Request, July 11, 1947; 12.
      - Hicks to Emspak Regarding Political Action Committee, September 18, 1947; 13.
      - Hicks to James Matles Regarding Finances and Factionalism, October 2, 1947; 14.
      - Hicks to Emspak Regarding Finances, October 17, 1947; 15.
      - Hicks to Matles Regarding Finances and Factionalism, October 20, 1947; 16.
      - Hicks to Russ Nixon Regarding Political Action Committee, November 13, 1947; 17.
      - Hicks to Emspak Regarding PAC, November 18-December 11, 1947; 18-19.
      - Hicks to Emspak Regarding Finances, August 3, 1949; 20.
      - Hicks to Emspak Regarding International Harvester Strike, October 2, 1952; 21.
    - Local 218 Outgoing Correspondence, February 9, 1944-April 26, 1945 (Box 8, Folder 92)
      - Fred Snow to Julius Emspak Regarding Local 218 Officers, February 9, 1944; 1.
      - Snow to Emspak Regarding Finances, June 28, 1944; 2.
      - Snow to Emspak Regarding Fellows Gear Shaper, August 15, 1944; 3.
      - Snow to Emspak Regarding Finances and Fellows Gear Shaper, September 8, 1944; 4.
      - Snow Telegram to UE Regarding 1944 UE Convention, September 15, 1944; 5.
      - Snow to UE Regarding Local 218 News and Finances, October 17, 1944; 6.
      - Snow to UE Regarding Local 218 Officers, October 19, 1944; 7.
      - Snow to UE Regarding Finances, October 20, 1944; 8.
      - Snow to UE Regarding Finances and Factionalism, October 26, 1944; 9.